bitrhymes.com 2018-10-24

# 

**GSN PRIVACY POLICY**

Effective Date: May 24, 2018

Please read this Privacy Policy and the related [GSN Terms of Service](http://gsngamesnetwork.com/terms.html) before using any GSN website, application or community feature.

Game Show Network, LLC and subsidiaries (collectively **“GSN” or “we”, “our”, or “us”** ) are committed to protecting your privacy and take the protection of your personal data very seriously.  This privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) explains how we collect, use and share the personal data that you provide to us and that we collect when you use any of our websites (each, a “ **Website** ”) mobile applications (each, an “ **App** ”), and our chat service, message boards, email service, messaging services, file communities, virtual communities, virtual assets, polls, surveys, and similar services (each, a **“Community Feature”** )  (unless a different policy is provided on a particular Website, App, or Community Feature, in which case such different policy will control). The Website, Apps and Community Features are collectively referred to as the  **“Services.”   **

**If you are located in the European Union (“EU”) or the U.K.** , this Privacy Policy also informs you about the management of your personal data and your rights in accordance with Article 13 of the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). 

**Data Controller**

GSN is the entity responsible for determining the means and purposes of processing personal data (i.e., the data controller) under this Privacy Policy and can be contacted as explained below in the How To Contact Us section.  GSN has appointed a Data Protection Officer for issues related to personal data in the EU and U.K., who can be contacted at **dpo@gsngames.com**.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We ask that you read this Privacy Policy from time to time.  We may modify it at any time in our sole discretion.  If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy that increase our rights to use personal data that we have previously collected about you, we will obtain your consent, where required by law, either through your registered email address or by prominent posting on the Services.  If you are an individual located outside of the EU or the U.K., your use of the Services indicates that you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Personal Data We Collect About You

How We Protect Children’s Privacy

How We Use Personal Data We Collect About You

When We Share Your Personal Data

Cookie Policy

Third-Party Advertisers and Third-Party Analytics

How We Protect Your Personal Data

Data Retention

Links to Other Websites

Location and Transfer of Personal Data

Notice to Residents of California

Notice to Residents of the EU and the U.K. 

Legal Basis for Processing

Rights of Individuals Located in the EU or U.K.

Lodging a Complaint

How You Can Contact Us

**Personal Data We Collect About You**

GSN collects the following types of personal data to provide visitors, users and players with our Services and information relevant to your needs and interests:

**Personal data you give us:   **You may give us personal data in a number of ways, including when you register to use our Services, receive offers, communicate with customer service, enter contests and accept prizes, and when you and create a personal profile. 

  * **GSN Accounts** : When you use certain Services, you may be required to register and create an account ( **“GSN Account”** ).  You may be asked to choose a user name and password and to provide some or all of the following personal data, depending on which Service you use:

  * Your real name
  * Date of birth
  * Gender
  * Postal address
  * Email address
  * Phone number

Please note that your user name and the city where you reside may be visible to other GSN users, depending on which Service you are using.  In addition, when you make a purchase through our Services, either we or our third-party payment processor service provider will collect billing information, such as payment card information, and we will keep data about your transaction history and any sweepstakes and other contests that you enter. 

  * **Community Features:** When you use our Community Features, your user name will be displayed, as will any content that you post.  Some message boards may also display your IP address.  All postings on Community Features will generally be available to, and freely accessible by, other users, and in some cases the general public. Because information posted will not be kept private, users should  exercise discretion when using Community Features. 

  * **Facebook:** GSN may allow you to sign in and associate your Facebook account with the Services.  When you do so, you allow GSN to access certain information from your Facebook profile that you have made available to be shared, including your Facebook ID, name, photo, and date of birth, and to use it (such as by posting your photo and name) in accordance with Facebook’s terms of use, this Privacy Policy, and GSN’s Terms of Service.  Please refer to the privacy settings on Facebook for information about what data is shared with GSN and to manage sharing through your account.

You can use some aspects of the Services at any time without providing any personal data. While providing personal data is voluntary, you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in some of the Services, if you choose not to share it.

**Personal data we get from third parties:** We also collect personal data about you (such as name, address, device IDs, location, service provider, and usage and player information) from third parties, such as advertising partners, platforms, customer rights management vendors, analytics companies, co-branded marketers, help desk vendors, and fraud detection companies. We use this data to improve the quality and relevance of the advertisements you see, improve the functionality of the Services, enable you to enter into competitions, or let you know of new developments in the Services. In the event that we receive such data and combine it with our customer records, the combined information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Personal data we collect automatically:** We automatically collect information about the devices that you use to interact with the Services, as well as information about how you interact with the Services. We use this data to provide the Services to you.  The information that we automatically collect may include the following, depending on which Service you are using:

  * Your IP Address;
  * Device identifier;
  * Web browser type and version;
  * Operating system;
  * Time zone;
  * Web browsing;
  * Location based upon IP Address;
  * Precise geolocation of mobile device;
  * GSN usage history;
  * GSN game history and skill level;
  * Page/app views; and
  * Language.

**How We Protect Children’s Privacy**

GSN Services are general audience sites not directed at children under the age of 18.  If we obtain actual knowledge that any information we collect has been provided by an individual under the age of 18, we will promptly delete that information.

If you are a parent or guardian who has discovered that your child has submitted his or her personal data to GSN, please send an email to help@gsngames.com to request deletion of that information.  Please be sure to include in your message the same user name and password that your child submitted. 

**How We Use Personal Data We Collect About You**

We may use your personal data for the following purposes:

**Communicate With You**

  * To provide you with customer support;
  * To communicate with you about our products and services, including promotions and offers;
  * To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may interest you; and
  * To let you know about new developments in the Services.

**Manage and Improve Our Business Operations**

  * To provide you with access to the Services;
  * To accept and process payments in connection with the Services;
  * To improve your experience using the Services;
  * To improve the functionality of the Apps;
  * To enable you to enter competitions;
  * For internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Services, when you choose to do so;
  * To measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others;
  * To deliver relevant advertising to you; and
  * To assist us in developing new products and improving our Services.

**Ensure a Secure Online Environment and Comply with Legal Obligations**

  * Protect against and detect fraud, abuse or other unlawful activity;
  * Enforce our Terms of Service, other corporate policies and industry standards; and
  * Comply with all applicable laws and reporting obligations.

**Unsubscribing From Communications:** GSN would like to use your personal data to communicate with you directly, via email, push notifications or direct mail, about products you have purchased and other related products and services we believe may be of interest to you, as well as related customer support.  If you no longer want to be contacted, you may update your email preferences by using the “Unsubscribe” link found in emails we send to you or by contacting us at **[help@gsngames.com](mailto:help@gsngames.com)**.  To disable push notifications, access Settings on your device and select the App(s) you no longer wish to receive push notifications from.

**When We Share Your Personal Data**

**With Our Owners and Other Related Entities:** We may share your personal data with our owners and other related entities, including Sony Pictures Entertainment, AT&T, and their parents, subsidiaries, or affiliated companies, in order to provide portions of the Services or to provide other support for a GSN promotion. Please refer to the individual privacy policies of our related entities for details concerning how they handle your personal data.

**To Support Business Services** **:** We may share your personal data with third parties who perform services on our behalf to support our business operations, including the following:

  * Product and/or experience customization;
  * Distribution of marketing and promotional material;
  * Website evaluation;
  * Data collection, storage, management, analysis and, where applicable, deletion; and
  * Other services to support our business operations, such as ad delivery and analysis. 

**To Provide Company Security** **:** We may disclose personal data when we determine that doing so is appropriate to:

  * Verify compliance with and enforce our Terms of Service and other policies governing our Services;
  * Protect our property, services and legal rights;
  * Protect personal safety or the property of others;
  * Respond to lawful requests from governmental authorities;
  * Comply with applicable laws; and
  * Support auditing, compliance and corporate governance functions.

**To Offer Promotions** : If you are a resident of the U.S. or Canada, you may participate in contests, sweepstakes or promotions in connection with our Services ( **“Promotions”** ).  (EU and U.K. residents are not eligible to participate.)  Such Promotions may be sponsored by or co-branded with a third party, who may obtain personal data that you submit in connection with the Promotions.  We cannot control those third parties’ use of such data. If you do not want your personal data to be collected by or shared with such a third party, do not participate in these Promotions. 

When entering a Promotion, we may ask for your consent to use your personal data or other information (such as name, voice or likeness) in advertising, promotional and marketing materials.

**To Extend Third-Party Offers** **:  **We may send you promotional mailings on behalf of third-party organizations that provide game-related offers and other offers.  If you sign up for the third-party offer, we will share your GSN Account information with the third-party offer provider. 

If you are a resident of the EU or the U.K., we will obtain your consent before using or sharing your information in this manner.

**In the Event of Corporate Change** : We may disclose, sell or transfer all information related to the Services, including personal data:

  * To a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of one or more of the Services; or
  * In connection with a corporate merger, consolidation or restructuring; the sale of substantially all of our stock and/or assets; or other corporate change, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process.

You will be notified by e-mail or prominent notice on our Website  or in App prior to a change of ownership or control of your personal data, if your personal data will be used contrary to this policy. 

**For Statistical Analysis** **:** We may disclose non-identifying, aggregated user statistics, such as the number of users who used the Services during a specific time period, to third parties for a variety of purposes, including describing our Services to prospective partners and other third parties. 

**Cookie Policy**

Our Services may place small data files on your computer or mobile device.  These data files may be cookies, pixel tags, e-tags, or other local storage provided by your browser or Apps (collectively “ **Cookies** ”). 

Some of these Cookies are technical (i.e., they allow us to provide the Services) and some are non-technical (i.e., they provide analytics about the use of our Services, allow us to remember your preferences, or facilitate advertising).  We also use third-party advertisers (each, a **“Third-Party Advertiser”** ) to market, sell and display advertisements on our Services. These Third-Party Advertisers may recognize Cookies we have placed (or place their own Cookie) on your device to collect information about your use of the Services for use in connection with their advertising activities.   

**How we use Cookies**

We use both persistent and session Cookies.  Persistent Cookies are used to improve your experience on our Services.  This includes, for example, recording your acceptance of our Cookie Policy to remove the Cookie message that first appears when you use our Services. Session Cookies are temporary and are deleted from your device when your web browser closes.  We use session Cookies to help us track internet usage.

We will not keep the personal data that we collect through Cookies for longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes mentioned in this Privacy Policy.

**Types of Cookies**

**Cookie Type**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---  
  
Strictly necessary/ Technical 

| 

These Cookies are necessary to allow us to operate the Services so you may access them as you have requested. These Cookies, for example, let us recognize that you have created an account and have logged into that account to access content through the Services. They also include Cookies that enable us to remember your previous actions within the same browsing session and secure the Services.  
  
Analytical /Performance

| 

These Cookies are used by us or our business partners to analyze how the Services are used and how they are performing. For example, these Cookies track what pages are most frequently visited, and what locations our visitors come from. If you subscribe to a newsletter or otherwise register with the Services, these Cookies may be correlated to you. These Cookies include, for example, Google Analytics Cookies.  
  
Functionality

| 

These Cookies let us operate the Services in accordance with the choices you make. These Cookies permit us to "remember" you in between visits. For instance, we will recognize your user name and remember how you customized the Services, for example by adjusting text size, fonts, languages and other parts of web pages that are alterable, and provide you with the same customizations during future visits.  
  
Third-Party Advertising

| 

We may allow our business partners to use Cookies on our Services for the same purposes identified above, including collecting information about your online activities over time and across different websites. The business partners that generate these Cookies, such as Adobe and Google, have their own privacy policies, and may use their Cookies to target advertising to you on other websites, based on use of the Services.  
  
**How to delete Cookies**

Most web browsers accept Cookies automatically.  However, you can delete Cookies manually or set your browser to automatically delete Cookies on a pre-determined schedule.  Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new Cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new Cookie and how to disable existing Cookies.  You can find out how to do this for your particular browser by clicking “help” on your browser's menu or by visiting www.allaboutcookies.org.   

Please note that if you decline to accept Cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features of the Services. 

Most browsers allow users to use a “private mode” by which Cookies are deleted after your website visit.  Please read the help section of your browser to learn more about how to activate the “private mode.”  You can still visit our website if your browser is in “private mode,” however, the user experience may not be optimal and some utilities may not work.

If you want to remove previously-stored Cookies, you can manually delete the Cookies at any time. However, this will not prevent the Services from placing further Cookies on your device unless and until you adjust your browser setting as described above.

For more information on the development of user-profiles and the use of targeting/advertising Cookies, please see www.youronlinechoices.eu, if you are located in the EU, or www.aboutads.info/choices, if in the United States.

**Adobe Flash Player**

Our Services enable the use of the Adobe Flash Player, which generates “flash cookies” by default.  Flash cookies remember user settings, preferences and usage similar to the browser Cookies referenced above, but flash cookies can store more information than browser Cookies and are managed through a different interface than the one provided by your web browser. 

You can control the degree to which you accept flash cookies by accessing your Adobe Flash Player management tools directly through the settings manager for Adobe Flash, located at http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html.  If you do not allow flash cookies to take any disc space on your computer, you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features on the Service. 

**Web Beacons**  

Our web pages or e-mail messages may contain a small graphic image called a web beacon which allows us to monitor and collect certain limited information about our users, such as the type of browser requesting the web beacon, the IP address of the computer that the web beacon is sent to and the time the web beacon was viewed. We may use web beacons to count visitors to our web pages or to monitor how our users navigate our Services, and we may include web beacons in e-mail messages in order to count how many of the messages we sent were actually opened or acted upon.

**IP Addresses**  

An IP Address is a number that is assigned to your mobile device, computer or network when you are linked to the Internet.  When you request pages from our Services, our servers log your IP Address. We may use IP Addresses for a number of purposes, such as system administration, to report aggregate information to our business partners or to audit the use of the Services.  We may associate your IP address with other personal data you provide.

**Third-Party Advertisers and Third-Party Analytics**

**Ad Serving Technology**

Third-party advertising companies (each, a **“Third-Party Ad Company”** ), also may use Cookies, clear GIFs, web beacons or other technologies to collect information to ensure that appropriate advertising is delivered when you use the Services, calculate or control the number of unique and repeat views of a given ad, deliver ads that relate to your interests, and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. 

The data that Third-Party Ad Company may collect for this purpose includes your IP address; device ID; information about your software, applications and hardware; machine or device make and model; advertisement(s) served; in-game location; length of time an advertisement was visible; other Internet and website usage information; web pages and mobile Internet sites which have been viewed by you (as well as date and time); domain type; size of the advertisement; advertisement response (if any); and angle of view.  If you click on an ad that appears on the Services, data, such as your IP address, may be revealed to the advertiser (or the applicable Third-Party Ad Company).

The Third-Party Ad Company that deliver ads may combine the personal data collected with other information they have independently collected from other services or products.  The collection and use by Third-Party Ad Company of personal data obtained through the Services and information they have independently collected from other services or products is governed by their own privacy policies. 

In addition, GSN uses pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partners (each, a “ **Management Partner** ”), who use them to recognize a unique Cookie placed by us or by another advertiser who works with the applicable Management Partner.  The Management Partner may set and access its own Cookies on your web browser in order to serve ads it believes may be of interest to you based on the profile information you provided to us at registration (e.g., demographic information), your browsing behavior on the Services, as well as information collected about you by the applicable Management Partner elsewhere online.  Management Partners may use information about you gathered from the Services to serve third-party ads to you elsewhere on the Internet. 

**Analytics**

GSN uses third-party web analytics services that collect and analyze our users’ data, such as device ID and IP address, to provide us with statistical information, such as where our users are located in the world, what content users view on our Services, and the size of our user base.  We use this information to improve and personalize our Services.

**How We Protect Your Personal Data**

GSN has implemented an information security program that includes physical, technical and procedural safeguards designed to protect your personal data. 

**Data Retention**

GSN will retain your personal data as needed to provide you with access to our Services and/or for as long as is necessary for the protection and pursuit of our legal rights and obligations under any laws that are applicable to our operations. 

**Links to Other Websites**

The Services may contain links to, or advertisements concerning, other websites. Other websites may also reference, advertise, or link to GSN. GSN is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. You should check the applicable privacy policy of any website you access through the Services.

**Location and Transfer of Personal Data**

Personal data you provide to us and through our Services may be stored on servers, databases and with third-party service providers in the United States and other countries whose data protection laws may differ from the jurisdiction in which you live.  When we transfer personal information from the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and the U.K., we put in place appropriate safeguards to ensure the safe and secure transfer  and handling of such data.

**Notice to Residents of California**

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to opt out of the disclosure of your personal data by GSN to third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes.  To make a request to opt out of such disclosure, please send an email to **[help@gsngames.com](mailto:help@gsngames.com)** or write us at 100 Summer Street, Boston, MA 02110.  You must include the Services as the subject line, and your full name, e-mail address, and postal address in your message.

**Notice to Residents of the EU and the U.K.**

If you are located in the EU or the U.K., you have certain rights with respect to your personal data.  If you would like to exercise those rights, please contact us at the email address below applicable to the App or Website you are using or through the menu options in the App.

For Bingo Bash

For: (i) GSN Casino; (ii) Grand Casino; (iii) Mirrorball Slots; and (iv) Slots Bash

For TriPeaks Solitaire

For: (i) WorldWinner; and (ii) gsn.com

For: (i) Fresh Deck Poker; and (ii) Wheel of Fortune Slots

**Legal Basis for Processing**

We will rely on the following legal bases for processing your personal data, depending on our purpose for such processing.

**You have consented to the processing of your personal data:   **We will obtain your consent before using or sharing your data for advertising that is targeted based on your browsing history, online behavior or other personal data that we or third parties may have collected about you. If you consent to our use of your personal data for any purpose, you have the right to withdraw consent at any time by contacting us, as explained above, or through the App in which you provided consent.

**We have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data:** GSN has a legitimate interest in processing your personal data for certain business and security purposes and to comply with applicable laws, including, but not limited to, the following:

  * Product and Service development, management, delivery and enhancement;
  * Fraud detection and prevention;
  * Network and system security;
  * General corporate operations;
  * User personalization;
  * Compliance with applicable foreign laws;
  * Communications regarding products and services that you have purchased; and
  * Non-targeted marketing and advertising.

You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data based on our legitimate interests.  You can do so by contacting us through the App(s) you are using, as described above.  The processing of some types of personal data is necessary to provide you the Services, however.  Therefore, if you object to certain types of processing, we may not be able to provide you the Services.

**Processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation:**   We will process personal data when necessary to comply with an obligation under EU or EU Member State law.

If we intend to use personal data that we have collected for a different purpose than was described to you, we will provide you with information about this secondary purpose and any additional information necessary to ensure fair and transparent processing, before we engage in further processing.

**Rights of Individuals Located in the EU or U.K.**

If you are located in the EU and U.K., you have the following rights, subject to applicable exceptions, under the GDPR and U.K. data protection laws:

**Right of access:** You have the right to obtain confirmation as to whether we are processing personal data about you, and if so, request a copy of the personal data.  If you are located in the EU or U.K. and you would like a copy of the personal data that GSN holds about you, please send a description of the personal data you would like a copy of and proof of your identity to the emails set forth above.

**Right to correction:** You have the right to correct any inaccuracies in the personal data we hold about you and, where applicable, complete any incomplete personal data that we hold.

**Right to erasure** : You have the right to request that GSN erase the personal data that we hold about you, if one of the conditions in Article 17 of the GDPR applies.

**Right to restriction of processing:** You have the right to restrict our processing of your personal data, if one of the conditions in Article 18 of the GDPR applies.

**Right to data portability:** You have the right to receive personal data concerning you in a structured, common and machine-readable format or request transmission of the data to a third party, if the conditions in Article 20 of the GDPR are met.

**Right to object:** You have the right to object to processing of your personal data based on our legitimate interests at any time.  We will no longer process the data, unless there are compelling legitimate grounds for our processing that override the interests, rights and freedoms of the data subject, or the processing serves the purpose of asserting, exercising or defending legal claims.

**Right to withdraw consent:** If we are processing your personal data based on your consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.

If you are located in the EU or U.K. and you would like to invoke any of these rights (other than “access,” which is explained above), you can make the appropriate change through your GSN Account, or you can contact us through the App(s) you are using, as described above.

**Lodging a Complaint**

Under Article 77 of the GDPR, if you are located in the EU or the U.K., you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you believe that the processing of your personal data infringes your rights under the GDPR.  The right to lodge a complaint may be invoked in the EU Member State in which you reside, in which you work or where the alleged infringement occurred.

**How You Can Contact Us**

GSN is dedicated to protecting your personal data and welcomes comments and questions on this Privacy Policy. You may e-mail us at the following address:

GSN Games

Attn: Privacy Help

100 Summer Street

Boston, MA 02110

USA

help@gsngames.com

© 2018 Game Show Network, LLC. and GSN Games, Inc.  All rights reserved.
